In today's video I am going to tell you
how you can insure your bike or car yourself from your mobile sitting at home, whatever I tell you, I will
tell you in detail, if you have
time then definitely watch this, I am going to show you step
by step and for this reason,
I am going to show you how to get
insurance and how to get a
soft copy, from where to
download the app, I will tell you the total
process, let's start the video chat,
if you want to insure your bike from your mobile phone,
then you can do it easily, for this
you have to open the Chrome browser,
when the Chrome browser opens
and you are seeing the search bar, here
you have to type Policy Bazaar, here
I typed Policy Bazaar and
when I open it, I will search
and here the first website that comes is
policybajaar.com, you are seeing it, you have to
click on this website and when you open it, the
center will be fresh in front of you like this,
you can insure many things from here, whether it is
car insurance,
bike insurance or this, when you are
looking at cycle insurance, you have to click on it,
click here so that  In this, the page will
open like this, now what you have to do here is to
enter your vehicle number here and after entering it, click on the Vivo price,
so let's enter the bike number here and
click on any price and you can see a
popup window opens in front of you like this
and here it is asking
which policy you had once, which
policy was it, stand and that is,
Aquarius fit third party job, you have to
select it here, like
Meghvanshi, if you do not know the third party, you
can click on don't remember, then
select it here, like this the
page will open here, here the details of the
vehicle number will be given
below like this, now
what you have to do,
look here on the right side, there are three options above, you can
cover it in this way, if you
click on Congress,
whichever company is in that party and
subscribe here, then here you can see the
company and you can say
whichever you like, you can save it here or
if you want  If you do
not do the first part i.e. company then you can also add a third party,
see here below whichever
you like, whichever company you like, you
can take it, if you want to do a third party,
here write 'Third Party Only',
fill in the 'Third Party Only' box,
when you click on it, see all the third party
companies, there are 17 third
party plans and here you can see the company, you
can see the price here, if you
slide down then more companies will be visible, it will be
visible here only and
see here whether there is any other plan or not, for how many
years do you want to do the policy, for one year, for
2 years, for 3 years, for how many
years you want to do the policy, from here
you select the time and you
can click on it only from here, like I
click on it here, you have to
click on the price, remember to
click on the flight, after that this
kind of detail will open in front, see here, this is
my company, from which company I am taking the policy
and after that how much
amount is going to be charged, you can see that here, it is
758 above and  First of all you have to go through three
steps, in the first step there will be a
name here, you can edit it by clicking on edit, you have to
enter the mobile number here and if there is a mobile number then you will
enter it, you have to enter the email ID here, this is the
mobile number email ID, it is necessary, now
enter it, the address will be visible here, you can change the address here, here in the
last you have to enter the pin code,
what you have to do in this way and you have to match it again,
remember that you enter the mobile number email ID
yourself, click on continue below it,
click on continue for the second step, as soon as you click on continue, the
page of the second step will
open here, you have to enter the name normally, so
let's go here, nominee, now whatever you had
entered normally, what is your relation with him, you have to
select everything here, so
whatever relation is there, flatten it, now the name
of the nominee has to be entered here,
so we can enter it by clicking and sliding here
and here it is asking whether the
income of the car finance, from here click yes and
continue and thirdly
In the step, see here what to do,
you can see the Garlic number here,
now in the previous Israni it will be there, from here you have to
select which company you had insured before
and after selecting it, now this policy
number, if you have insured first then you have to
enter the policy number of that company there and the expiry date and the
expiry date of the previous policy,
you have to select it here and put it
and the registration date will
automatically appear here, if it is not appearing then you
can select Adjust from here,
now do not ask when you had planned this policy, you have to
click on two in it, there is
fee here but let it remain stuck and
see here it is asking whether you have
added it by selecting it here, what do
you have to do now, if you click next then the answer will
come in front of you like this, now
see here you will get the option to make payment,
here you will see how much is your Bhairu of the vehicle
there and how much premium is going to be charged,
GST is given here and
your total is given below here  You
can see it is above, that is, you have to
pay the total amount with GST. If you
want to get its update in WhatsApp, you
can enable it. Now the PSC
is clear. Security has to be clicked on it.
As soon as you click on it, your payment gateway will
open here. See, my
payment voucher has opened. Now you have to
select the matter for making the payment.
Mode Tilak Karna Karna, Net Banking
UP, if you want to do that also,
you can select it. So let me
show you how to make the payment from here. If you
click here, then see it has
come here. If you use BHIM also,
on Google, you can select it on the phone here
or you can click on the QR code
below here. You will
click on the advertisement code here. The QR code will appear here.
You can also make the payment by scanning it.
If you want to make the second payment,
click on the Dhar app. Here
you have to enter UP like this. And here
add this account and make payment.
Click on it. Then whoever you entered will
send the payment request to you, you can see it.
I had entered Paytm and
my payment request has come in Paytm when you
unlock Paytm here then this
note will be visible here and what you have to do is
you have to make the payment here like you
will make the payment here and like the payment of the ring will be
confirmed here and your
payment will be successful here so keep this in
mind you should not cut it, if you have to search
then switch and
come to the same website here and you have to pay attention to one thing
I always tell the truth
you should not refresh here if you do a
difference then your payment will not be made, the
payment will stop, it will get stuck,
after that here you will automatically see that your
payment will be made and see here it is
written that
after 30 minutes you will be sent a soft copy of the MLA you had entered
and look here here the
details of the optional pool are compressed here you can see the details here
let me check my mail after half an hour
so my half hour is over
here I open my mail
as if I scan the mail see here
my mail is done from the policy side  That
means my paper of Saumya Anil Insurance has
come here, you can see here it is
written that my issue has been done
and my soft copy has been
sent as attachment here,
you can download your soft copy by clicking on download,
like mine has been
downloaded, let me open it and
show where is the policy number
and my details will be from total here, you
can see this is my company and this is my
soft copy i.e. insurance paper, you can
print it out and keep it,
I will zoom in and show you, you can see
my policy number is given here and
see here from two wheeler insurance and if you
select below then here I will show you, see
here my name is visible,
address is Iyer, customer ID,
mobile number, email ID, portal is showing something here,
now you know how to do bike insurance from mobile
in the village
[
Music]